[{"answer": "Who is this", "docId": "American-Graffiti.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "You callin' from that place, that place", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Long distance", "docId": "American-Graffiti.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "All we got is you", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Hey, you're new around here. Where're you from", "docId": "American-Graffiti.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "that place? You know a guy named my friend", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "that place? You know a guy named my friend", "docId": "American-Graffiti.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Well, he used to. He goes to J.C. now", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "No. Does he go to that place High", "docId": "American-Graffiti.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Do you go to J.C.", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Ah, shit", "docId": "American-Graffiti.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I'm too old for you", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Old enough. How old are you", "docId": "American-Graffiti.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "You can't be that old", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Hey, nobody can beat him, man. He's got the fastes", "docId": "American-Graffiti.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Right..", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I ain't nobody, dork. Right", "docId": "American-Graffiti.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Hey, you see this my friend, you tell him I'm lookin' for him, huh? Tell him I aim to blow his ass right off the road", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "No shi", "docId": "American-Graffiti.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Oh yea", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Wel", "docId": "American-Graffiti.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Fine. Great. How've you been", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " Well, you mind if I come along", "docId": "American-Graffiti.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Okay", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Help, wait! Jok", "docId": "American-Graffiti.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Excuse m", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Hiya, my friend. Say, do you think if I brought my Mopar by the shop Monday you could spot weld the bumper bracket", "docId": "American-Graffiti.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Sure. Hey, have you met my friend", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Could yo", "docId": "American-Graffiti.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Great. Quarter to twelve. Thanks a lot", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Hi. Still quarter to twelve", "docId": "American-Graffiti.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Night", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Yes. Collect Call", "docId": "American-Graffiti.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Sir, this is the Operator", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Your name is my friend", "docId": "American-Graffiti.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Are you French, Operator", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "I... I love you, Operator", "docId": "American-Graffiti.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Is my friend there", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "American-Graffiti.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "I'm thirteen, how old are you", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "You know, it doesn't make sense to leave home to look for a home, to give up a life to find a new life, to say goodbye to friends you love just to find new friends", "docId": "American-Graffiti.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "That's what my friend said", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Hello", "docId": "American-Graffiti.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Hi", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Gee, ah, where's my friend, anyway", "docId": "American-Graffiti.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "You broke up? Bull", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "They say you're the fastest thing in the Valley. But that can't be your car, man. That must be your mama's car. Hell, I feel embarrassed just getting near ya", "docId": "American-Graffiti.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Field car? What's a Field Car", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "I was just wondering who she is", "docId": "American-Graffiti.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Price range? You mean she's ", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "No, thanks. U'mm. You know we got to report the car missing", "docId": "American-Graffiti.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Yeah. See yuh", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Listen, a", "docId": "American-Graffiti.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "Well, it's been building up inside of me like a volcano, all night. Maybe if I knew where you lived I could fight i", "docId": "American-Graffiti.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": " Two three on", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "Yeah. I like you. You're all right", "docId": "American-Graffiti.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "I, ah... I like you. Okay", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "Who is this on the Wolfman's telephone", "docId": "American-Graffiti.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "How're you doin', my friend", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "Jeez, did you show him! He'll probably never even get in a car again", "docId": "American-Graffiti.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "It was beautiful, my friend. Just beaut", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "American-Graffiti.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "Who were you expecting", "qsentId": 64}]